<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on CSV SOLUTIONS</title>
    <link>https://www.csvresearch.com/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on CSV SOLUTIONS</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 11:52:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.csvresearch.com/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Training and Capacity building</title>
      <link>https://www.csvresearch.com/services/training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.csvresearch.com/services/training/</guid>
      <description>Most of the services offered by data science consultants involve understanding business problems, reducing costs, increasing profits and shielding business from unforeseen future losses. The main objective of csv solutions is to do just this. Some of the services we offer are:-
Training and capacity building Wevelopment of capacity through continuous learning is very important. Our teaching is majorly focus on practical projects that are based on hand-on examples. We offer training in the following fields:-</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://www.csvresearch.com/services/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.csvresearch.com/services/research/</guid>
      <description>We offer research from that links researcher across the globe. We also offer professional consultancy on:-
 Proposal writing Grants and funding project design and implementation monitoring and evaluation Market research analysis  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dashboard Development and shiny applications</title>
      <link>https://www.csvresearch.com/services/dashboard-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.csvresearch.com/services/dashboard-development/</guid>
      <description>They say statistics scale well but visualization explains better. The major aim of analysis is to understand what is going on with the products and what the trends are.Our major tasks are to:-
 Produce rapidly develop high quality dashboards Supporting of full stack data scientist to navigate the metrics in the dashboards( from setting up the UI&amp;rsquo;s to the server optimization) Best practice in dashboard designs variable from Tableau, Power BI to flex dashboards and Excel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Understanding</title>
      <link>https://www.csvresearch.com/services/business-understanding/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.csvresearch.com/services/business-understanding/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GIS analysis</title>
      <link>https://www.csvresearch.com/services/geospatial-information-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.csvresearch.com/services/geospatial-information-systems/</guid>
      <description>Being able to view analysis on maps has never been simpler. we offer this services as broken down below:-
 development of spatial databases Webscarping of geographical data Applied remote sensing Object based image analysis and classification Co-GIS land use, land cover and change detection  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Analysis</title>
      <link>https://www.csvresearch.com/services/data-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.csvresearch.com/services/data-analysis/</guid>
      <description>They say the future is in understanding data, well here we easily break down data for you. We provide expert consultation services from:-
 Database development using SQL Statistical computing and graphics in both R and Python Data wrangling Automation of analysis processses Dashboard development Web based Shiny applications designs  In the rise of AI, being at the forefront of machine learning and deep learning gives you a competitive advantage in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
